<resources>
    <!-- Administration for CDSS rules -->
    <string name="ui.admin.cdss.master.title">CDSS Library</string>
    <string name="ui.admin.cdss.master.help"><![CDATA[
    This page shows the master list of all registered Clinical Decision Support (CDSS) libraries in your installation of SanteDB. These libraries form the basis of any
    clinical protocols, decision support rules, and facts. Please be sure to read the <a href="https://help.santesuite.org/developers/applets/cdss-protocols" target="_blank">CDSS Documentation on the SanteSuite Wiki</a>
    before modifying these rules, as they may have an adverse impact on patient care.
    ]]></string>
    <string name="ui.admin.cdss.create.title">New CDSS Library</string>
    <string name="ui.admin.cdss.create.upload.option">Upload a CDSS Library File</string>
    <string name="ui.admin.cdss.create.manual.option">Manually Create a CDSS Library</string>
    <string name="ui.admin.cdss.create.upload.file">CDSS Library File</string>
    <string name="ui.admin.cdss.create.upload.file.hint"><![CDATA[Select a CDSS library definition file from your hard drive to import into the SanteDB instance. If you upload a file with an identifier or UUID matching an existing library, this will 
    update the existing file, otherwise the library will be imported]]></string>
    <string name="ui.admin.cdss.edit.upload">Upload Library</string>
    <string name="ui.admin.cdss.edit.upload.help">New Version of CDSS Library</string>
    <string name="ui.admin.cdss.edit.upload.help.text">
            <![CDATA[ 
            This tool is used to upload a new version of this CDSS library using a raw definition file. This option is useful if you are authoring your CDSS rules using the CDSS XML library format or the CDSS text format. This method of maintaining
            a CDSS library is preferred, since it provides complete access to the CDSS engine's functionality. Before continuing, please consult the 
            <a href="https://help.santesuite.org/developers/applets/cdss-protocols" target="_blank">CDSS Documentation on the SanteSuite Wiki</a> for more information about these formats.
            ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="org.santedb.widget.emr.cdssLibrary.logic">Logic</string>
    <string name="org.santedb.widget.emr.cdssLibrary.data">Reference Data</string>
    <string name="org.santedb.widget.emr.cdssLibrary.main">Library</string>
    <string name="org.santedb.widget.emr.cdssLibrary.main.attribute">Library Properties</string>
    <string name="org.santedb.widget.emr.cdssLibrary.logic.define">Logic Definitions</string>
    <string name="org.santedb.widget.emr.cdssLibrary.data.define">Reference Sets</string>
    <string name="org.santedb.widget.emr.cdssLibrary.main.history">Version History</string>
</resources>